Charles B. Gunn Collection 1988.0001
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
Charles B. Gunn Collection
undated, 1834-2002
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
1988.0001
10 Linear Feet
The Charles B. Gunn Collection consists of papers produced by and about Gunn, as well as materials he collected of historical information about the New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company, Penn Central, Amtrak, and Conrail. The collection includes photographs taken by Gunn when he served as official photographer for the New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company, in the mid-1950s.
Access
The collection is open and available for research.
Acquisition Information
The records were donated by Charles B. Gunn in 1988. A large addition of photographs of railroad stations in Connecticut, Massachusetts, and Rhode Island, most of them taken by Mr. Gunn in the mid-1950s, was donated by Mr. Robert N. Uricchio of Newington, Connecticut, in 2004.
Location of Copies or Alternate Formats
Digital reproductions of materials in this collection may also be found in the Archives & Special Collections digital repository.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged by format. The papers are arranged with personal information about and by Charles G. Gunn first, followed by materials organized alphabetically by subject. The illustrations, poster and diagrams are organized by type of item. The photographs are arranged by the following subseries: derailments and damage done to the railroad by natural disasters, railroad structures such as stations and bridges, and then other topics, including photographs of Gunn himself and New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company presidents George Alpert and Patrick B. McGinnis. The Flood of August 1955 photographs are organized by towns along the railroad routes. The scrapbooks consist of two volumes of photographs.
Series I: Papers (undated, 1834-2002) consists of papers collected by Charles B. Gunn about the railroads he worked for, including the New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company (a.k.a. New Haven Railroad), Penn Central, Amtrak and ConRail, as well as information about his career with the railroads, particularly when he served as official photographer in the mid-1950s. Much of the material is of photocopied newspaper articles and other literature about various railroad history topics. A few of the files hold materials produced by the railroad indicated, including a manuscript letter book from the Boston & Providence Railroad, files of departments of the New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company, and a volume of stockholders minutes of the Old Colony Railroad. The papers also include information about various presidents of the New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company, including Frederic C. Dumaine (1948-1951), Frederic C. ("Buck") Dumaine, Jr. (1951-1954), Patrick B. McGinnis (1954-1956), and George Alpert (1956-1961), and trustee Harry W. Dorrigan, who served after the 1961 reorganization. It also includes information about natural disasters that occurred in the northeast, particularly the Hurricane of 1938 and the Floods of 1955, and their effect on the railroad.
Series II: Illustrations, Poster and Diagrams (undated, 1937-1967) consists of equipment diagrams of diesel locomotives 0760-0786, flat cars, box cars, steel cabooses, and a sleeper car, as well as a hand brake and freight car wheels. It also includes freight train cut-out illustrations meant for children and a reprint of a 1855 poster advertising the Philadelphia, Niagara and Western railroad route.
Series III: Photographs (undated, 1927-1985). The photographs include those taken by staff at the New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company Public Relations Department, particularly by Gunn himself when he served as official company photographer in the mid-1950s. Subseries A consists of photographs of train derailments and the damage done to the railroad by the Hurricane of 1938 and the Floods of August and October 1955. Subseries B consists of images of railroad stations, and the construction of a highway bridge over railroad tracks in New Haven, Connecticut, in 1959. Subseries C includes other photographs of various topics, including company presidents such as Patrick B. McGinnis and George Alpert. Of special interest are photographs of Cuban president Fidel Castro at the New Haven, Connecticut, railroad station, when he visited the United States in 1959.
Series IV: Scrapbooks (1955) consists of two scrapbooks of large prints of aerial photographs of locations in Connecticut, Massachusetts, and Rhode Island devastated by the Floods of August 1955, taken by New Haven photographer and filmmaker Samuel Kravitt.
History
Charles B. Gunn was born on April 10, 1918, and grew up in New Haven, Connecticut. In 1936 he began his forty-four year railroad career as a clerk with the New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company. Over the years he worked for many departments of the company, including Accounting, Materials Accounting, Public Relations, Methods and Procedures, and the General Storekeeper's Office. His only time away from employment with the company was when he served for three and a half years in the Army during World War II.
Gunn is best known, though, as the official company photographer during the years of the Patrick B. McGinnis presidentcy of 1954 to 1956. Gunn traveled with McGinnis on inspection trips of the railroad line. He took hundreds of photographs of the devastation to railroad property and towns along the railroad routes from the floods of August and October 1955. After McGinnis left the company in January 1956 Gunn's position as official photographer was eliminated and he returned to work with other company departments, though he never stopped taking photographs of locomotives, stations, and other railroad-related scenes.
Gunn was still working for the New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company when it collapsed and emerged as a part of Penn Central on January 1, 1969. Penn Central soon disintegrated to become ConRail and Amtrak.
Gunn retired in 1980 but continued to work as a professional photographer of weddings and church events and as an active promoter of the history of southern New England railroads. He regularly attended railroad shows and sold prints of the photographs he produced for the New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad.
Charles B. Gunn died on April 12, 2002.
Custodial History
The materials were created or collected by Charles B. Gunn prior to their donation.
Scope and Content
The Charles B. Gunn Collection consists of papers produced by and about Gunn, as well as materials he collected of historical information about the New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company, Penn Central, Amtrak, and ConRail. The collection includes photographs taken by Gunn when he served as official photographer for the New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company, in the mid-1950s.
Separated Material
The following materials were removed from the collection and cataloged:
Transportation Association of America, Adjusting the Nation's Timepiece: The Story of the Uniform Time Act of 1966. (1966: Transportation Association of America, Washington, D.C.). [WTS 5]
Kalmbach, A.C., "Grand Central Terminal: New York City," reprinted from Trains and Travel. (undated) [XA I.12 no. 24]
New York Central System, Grand Central Terminal (undated) [XA I.12 no. 23]
The Thomaston Express, Disaster! The Big Flood, Friday, August 19, 1955: The Thomaston Story. Reprints from The Thomaston [Connecticut] Express, 1955. [XA I.12 no. 25]
Interstate Commerce Commission, The Interstate Commerce Act (1923: Government Printing Office, Washington, D.C.). [B6535]
Boston Chamber of Commerce, Boston, Massachusetts: A Manufacturing and Commercial Community Built Around an Historic Shrine (1928: Convention Bureau, Boston Chamber of Commerce, Boston, Mass.) [XA I.12 no. 20]
Facts and Figures covering the New Haven Railroad, 1922-1955. (New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company, 1955). [XA I.12 no. 21]
New England railroads. Dodd C6110
Interstate Commerce Act. Dodd B6535
June 1958 and November 1961 issues of Along the Line, published by and for the employees and friends of the New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Co. [Dodd Per]
Issues of Railroad News, published by the Railroad Department of the YMCA, New Haven Railroad. Issues include March 1898 (Vol. I, no. 5), July 1902 (Vol. V, no. 9), March 1905 (Vol. VIII, no. 5), April 1905 (Vol. VIII, no. 6), and June 1966 (Vol. 3, no. 1). [Dodd Per]
Connecticut (state); Massachusetts (state); Rhode Island (state); Photographs; Manuscripts (document genre); Photographers; Railroad accidents; Flood damage; Hurricanes; Publications (documents); Notebooks; Correspondence; Canaan (inhabited place); Floods; New Haven (inhabited place); History; New England (general region); Meriden (inhabited place); Notes; Railroad stations; Illustrations (layout features).; Railroads; New York (State); Financial Records; Minutes (administrative records); Maps (documents); East Hartford (Conn.); Administrative records; Hartford (inhabited place); Newsletters; Employees; Histories; Obituaries; Posters; ConRail; Dumaine, Frederic Christopher, 1866-1951; Grand Central Terminal (New York, N.Y.); Castro, Fidel, 1926-2016; Alpert, George; McGinnis, Patrick B.; Old Colony Railroad Company; Providence and Worcester Railroad Company; Pennsylvania Railroad; Kravitt, Samuel, 1913-2000; Pennsylvania Station (New York, N.Y.); Dumaine, Frederic C., Jr.; Gunn, Charles B.; Pennsylvania Station (New York, N.Y.)
- Series I: Papers, undated, 1834-2002
  - Subseries A: Personal Papers of and Information about Charles B. Gunn, 1948-2002 (Box 1)
    - Biographical information and personal papers, 1955-2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Books about railroad history in southern New England for which Gunn provided photographs and information, 1959, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bush, George H. W. (Vice-President ), Letters to and from, about a photograph Gunn took of Bush's father, Prescott Bush, in 1955, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Connecticut Historical Society, Information about a lecture and exhibit at, about Connecticut railroads, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Connecticut Railroads -- An Illustrated History, Information about and manuscript drafts of, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Information about the January 1959 issue of Modern Railroads with a front cover photograph by Gunn (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - New Haven Colony Historical Society, Letter from, to Gunn, thanking him for donation of photographs, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Photographs taken by Gunn, Information about, 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Suggestions made by Gunn for improvements to the operation of the railroad, 1948-1963 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Subseries B: Collected papers and records, undated, 1834-1988
    - Advertising flyers for commuter cars and the "Dan'l Webster", undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Alpert, George, undated, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Amtrak, 1971-1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Amtrak -- timetables, 1982-1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Boston & Maine Railroad and Guilford Transportation Industries, undated, 1981-1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Boston & Providence Railroad -- manuscript copies of letters written by Peter Pratt, attorney for the railroad, 1834-1841 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Cape Cod railroads, 1980, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Cedar Hill railroad yard, 1937, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - "Cities, Towns and Villages in Southern New England with Directions How to Reach Them," by H.W. Quinlan, Passenger Traffic Manager of the New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Commuter service along the New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company and the New Haven Division of Conrail and Amtrak, 1966, 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Connecticut Company (trolley lines), undated, 1968, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Connecticut Department of Transportation, Information about, with "State Rail Plan Update" (December 1982), undated, 1982-1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Conrail, 1975-1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Conrail -- union agreements with the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers and the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employes, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Cos Cob Power Plant, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Deregulation of railroads, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Dorrigan, Harry, 1961, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Dumaine, Frederic C. Jr. ("Buck"), 1953 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Equipment -- Box cars, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Equipment -- Locomotives, undated, 1938, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Equipment, Passenger, 1956, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Equipment, Summaries of, 1928, 1946-1968 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - "Facts and Figures Covering the New Haven Railroad, 1922-1955" (with annotations by H.J. Moorhead giving statistical information up to 1964), 1955-1964 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Farmington [Connecticut] Canal, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Flood -- "Disaster! The Big Flood, Friday, August 19, 1955: The Thomaston Story" (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Flood, Effect of, on the New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company, 1955, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Hurricane of September 21, 1938, 1938-1941 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - McGinnis, Patrick B., Writings by and information about, 1954-1958 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Maps of Connecticut Company, New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, and Conrail systems, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Map -- NYNH&HRR Density of Freight Traffic for a Normal Day (July 9, 1912), November 1912, revised 1913 (Box 22)
    - Model trains, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Narragansett Pier Railroad, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - National Association of Railroad Passengers, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Envelope 41)
    - Naugatuck River Line, 1982, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - New Haven Preservation Trust, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - New Haven Railroad Historical & Technical Association, 1983-1987 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company annual reports, 1946, 1947, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company -- bankruptcies and mergers with other railroad companies, 1952-1980 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company -- correspondence about the acquisition of Providence & Worcester Railroad stock, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company, Employees and others associated with, 1940s-1950s (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company, Employees of -- Guides and union information, 1942-1960 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company and predecessors -- historical information, 1913-1981 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company, Financial control of, 1953-1966 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company -- Petition to Connecticut Public Utility Commission and Massachusetts Department of Public Utilities to acquire and hold stock of railroad corporations (File 1730), 1926-1936 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company -- President's progress reports, 1956-1959 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company -- retirement of automatic signals from Hartford to East Hartford, Connecticut, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company -- special trains, undated, 1937, 1953-1958 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company, Electrical Transmissions & Communications Department -- correspondence and plans regarding construction of an overhead bridge for an access road to Riverside Park in Hartford, Connecticut, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company, Electrical Transmissions & Communications Department -- correspondence and plans regarding Park River Conduit and Capital Avenue Interchange (Route I-84) in Hartford, Connecticut, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company, Electrical Transmissions & Communications Department -- correspondence and plans regarding relocation of Route 6A in Meriden, Connecticut, 1962-1969 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company, Purchasing Department -- pricebook for supplies, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company, Travel Bureau -- vacation booklets for Boston, the Berkshires and Litchfield Hills, Cape Cod, Connecticut, Martha's Vineyard, Nantucket, and Rhode Island, undated (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company and Frederic C. Dumaine, Fortune Magazine article about, April 1949 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Northwest Corridor, Transportation in, 1975, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Old Colony Railroad -- stockholders minutes and bylaws, 1852-1890 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - "On Track," a monthly publication for Metro-North employees, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Penn Central Transportation Company, 1973-1981 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Penn Central Transportation Company, Employees of -- safety rules and pay, 1968, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Penn Central Transportation Company -- proposal for reorganization, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Penn Central Transportation Company -- timetables, New Haven region, 1969, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Piggyback cars, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Politics and the railroads, 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Poughkeepsie Railroad Bridge, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Providence & Worcester Railroad, 1980-1985 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Railroad stations -- Canaan, Connecticut, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Railroad stations -- Hartford, Connecticut, 1981, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Railroad stations -- New Haven, Connecticut, 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Railroad stations -- New York City -- Grand Central Terminal and Pennsylvania Station, 1946-1987 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Railroad stations -- various others, 1981-1985 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Strikes by railroad workers, 1963, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Timetables, Collecting and selling, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Train wrecks, including a derailment in Stamford, Connecticut, in January 1959 and in New Haven, Connecticut, on September 2, 1913, 1959, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Trains -- "Dan'l Webster" press kit, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Trains, Historic, of the New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company and predecessors, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Trains -- information about Talgo, Turbo Train, and Tank Train, undated, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Uniform Time Act, 1966 (notice about change to Pennsylvania Railroad timetables because of act) (Box 2, Folder 84)
- Series II: Illustrations, poster and diagrams, undated, 1937-1967
  - Illustrations -- Freight Train Cut-Outs, undated (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Reprint (1855) of a poster advertising the Philadelphia, Niagara and Western Railroad route, undated (Box 22)
  - Equipment diagrams, 1937-1967
    - Diesel locomotives 0760-0786, 1949, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - 70 Ton Flat Cars, 17200-17274, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Steel Box Car, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Highway Trailer Flat Car, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Steel Caboose, C-506 to C-509, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Steel Caboose, C-535 to C-584, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Steel Caboose, C-585 to C-634, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Steel Caboose, C-635 to C-709, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Stainless Steel Sheathed Streamlined 6 Section - 4 Bedroom - 6 Roomette Sleeper Cars, 527-537, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Non Spin Vertical Wheel Hand Brake Sealed Type, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Wheels - Wrought Steel One Wear and Multiple Wear Freight Cars, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 86)
- Series III: Photographs, undated, 1927-1985
  - Subseries A: Hurricanes, Floods and Derailments
    - Connecticut River Flood -- Hartford, Connecticut, and Holyoke, Massachusetts (1988-0001.ph10-ph23), 1927 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Hurricane of 1938, Norwich and Putnam, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph24-ph26) (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Hurricane of 1938 -- Niantic, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph27-ph30, 1988-0001.ph32-ph43 and 1988-0001.ph599) (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - Hurricane of 1938 -- New London, Connecticut -- includes images of the marooned light tender "Tulip" (1988-0001.ph44-ph70 and UC19-0003) (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Hurricane of 1938 -- Noank and Mystic, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph71-ph79 and UC19-0005) (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Hurricane of 1938 -- Stonington, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph80-ph100 and UC19-0006) (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Hurricane of 1938 -- locations unknown (1988-0001.ph101-ph111) (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Hurricane of 1938 -- Providence, Rhode Island (1988-0001.ph112) (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - Hurricane of 1938 -- along the Fairhaven Branch and Cape Cod, Massachusetts, locations, including Buzzards Bay and the Woods Hole Branch (1988-0001.ph113-ph116) (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - Hurricane on Cape Cod, Massachusetts (1988-0001.ph117-ph142), early 1940s (Box 4, Folder 96)
    - Hurricane -- Yalesville, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph143-ph166), early 1940s (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - Flooding -- unidentified locations (1988-0001.ph187-ph191), 1944 (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - Derailment of locomotive 3551 -- location unknown, probably Rhode Island (1988-0001.ph167-ph177), [post-1946] (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - Derailment of locomotive 3551 -- location unknown, probably Rhode Island (1988-0001.ph178-ph186), [post-1946] (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - Hurricane -- Stonington, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph192-ph207), September 1954 (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - Hurricane -- Stonington, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph208-ph223), September 1954 (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - Hurricane -- unknown location, possibly Cape Cod, Massachusetts (1988-0001.ph224-ph237), September 1954 (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - Hurricane -- Stonington, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph238-ph245), September 1954 (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - Derailment -- Danbury Branch (1988-0001.ph246-ph255), 1955 (Box 6, Folder 105)
    - Derailment -- East Walden, New York, on October 28, 1953 (1988-0001.ph256-ph270, UC19-0008, UC19-0009) (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - Derailment -- East Walden, New York, on October 28, 1953 (1988-0001.ph271-ph288) (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - Derailment -- Bridgeport, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph289-ph298, UC19-0010), July 1955 (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - Derailment -- Bridgeport, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph299-ph306), July 1955 (Box 6, Folder 109)
    - Derailment -- Bridgeport, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph307-ph321), July 1955 (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - Derailment -- Bridgeport, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph322-ph334), July 1955 (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - Derailment -- Bridgeport, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph335-ph349), July 1955 (Box 6, Folder 112)
    - Derailment -- Bridgeport, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph350-ph359), July 1955 (Box 6, Folder 113)
    - Derailment -- West Wareham, Massachusetts (1988-0001.ph360-ph368), July 26, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 114)
    - Derailment -- West Wareham, Massachusetts (1988-0001.ph369-ph394), July 26, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 115)
    - Flood damage -- New Milford, Connecticut, repair of Bridge 43.45 ("Gauntlet Bridge") over Housatonic River (1988-0001.ph395-ph400, UC19-0011), August 1955 (Box 7, Folder 116)
    - Flood damage -- Cornwall and West Cornwall, Connecticut, (1988-0001.ph401-ph404, UC19-0012), August 1955 (Box 7, Folder 117)
    - Flood damage -- Cornwall, Connecticut, bridge repair (1988-0001.ph405-ph413, UC19-0013), August 1955 (Box 7, Folder 118)